https://karenranney.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Menu HomeBooksComing SoonWhat’s NewBlogAbout MePrivacyWho I amThis is the website for author Karen Ranney. My website address is: https://karenranney.com.What personal data I collect and why I collect itCommentsWhen visitors leave comments on the site I collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment if you do use Gravatar.I do not use any information from the comments with the exclusion of your email address to contact you if you’ve won a drawing.MediaIf you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.CookiesIf you leave a comment on my site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.Embedded content from other websitesArticles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.AnalyticsWho I share your data withI don’t share your data with anyone. In other words, no third-party vendors or companies. I don’t use your data to sign you up for anything or retain the information for any purpose other than the following comment metadata.How long I retain your dataIf you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so I can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.What rights you have over your dataIf you have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data I hold about you, including any data you have provided to the website. You can also request that I erase any personal data I hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.Where I send your dataVisitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service. I currently utilize two separate spam detection services.My contact informationIf you have any concerns, please email me at karen@karenranney.com.Additional informationHow I protect your dataMy hosting service is security conscious plus I also offer two factor authentication if you sign up for my newsletter.What data breach procedures I have in placeBecause my hosting service is security conscious I receive reports from them in the case of any data breaches. I have not experienced any data breaches in the past five years.What third parties I receive data fromI receive no third party information.
Search for:
https://karenranney.com/wp-content/uploads/To_Bed_the_Bride-1.mp4
Instagram
Twitter
Facebook
Subscribe to Blog via Email
Email Address
Recent Commentswillaful on Rode Hard and Put Away WetSDF on Rode Hard and Put Away WetLinda Cohen on Rode Hard and Put Away Wetdenise on Without God Are We Good?Zella Elder on Without God Are We Good?Annette N on Without God Are We Good?Rowena Mayes on Without God Are We Good?Jeanne Sheats on Without God Are We Good?Ivy Truitt on Without God Are We Good?Zella Elder on Rode Hard and Put Away Wet Subscribe to my newsletter.
SUBSCRIBE!
Thank you! You've successfully subscribed. Recent Posts Without God Are We Good? Profundities in the Morning Rode Hard and Put Away Wet Food and Disease, Canine Style Unforgotten There Must Be a Pony in Here Somewhere No Comment Necessary Connections More Bits and Bobs Terrific Tuesday!
